I keep my windows open when I sleep
I like being cold and hearing the rain
And I've moved a lot in the past few years
The longest I've stayed in a place was my one bedroom apartment on 5th ave
It's a major street that runs downtown
And to a number of hospitals
Train tracks run parallel to the road
Then I moved to Ohio
It was strange and quiet
So dark
I had a hard time adjusting to the silence
And then the relationship that moved me there shattered
I left Ohio and had to stay with my parents while I was between places
In their new home by the woods
It was loud
Like I was used to
But with unfamiliar noise
I moved back to the city in the beginning of November
It was a warm November
My windows were open - the rain falling outside
I finally felt at home again
And when I could hear the train again
My heart soared